https://rockingham.insure/privacy-policy/

Questions regarding your automatic monthly payment? Click here.
Dan Harris
Daniel Harris Insurance Agency, Inc.
Privacy Policy
Rockingham Insurance values your privacy. We are committed to informing consumers about the information we collect and utilize.
View the Rockingham Privacy Policy.
Personal Information
Rockingham Insurance may ask for personally identifying information such as your address, complete name, and other essential contact information. We use this information to process or respond to your requests for information or services.
Links
Links to third party sites are on the Rockingham Insurance site. We do not control the content, operation, or privacy practices of these sites. Clicking on one of these links will take you to an external website. Rockingham Insurance is not responsible for these links.
Corporate Privacy Policy
The Rockingham Insurance Statement of Privacy Principles governs our use of customer information.
Fill out the form below to opt-out of the Rockingham Insurance Information Sharing Policy.
Policyholder Name*
First
Last
Policy Number(s)*Indicate all policy numbers to update communication status.Phone Number- For account verification only.I wish to opt-out of Rockingham Insurance's Privacy Policy.*
Yes
Change previous selection
Policy Changes / Questions
The online Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Changes are available on this page for review.
If you have specific questions regarding this or another privacy statement, please contact us by calling 1-800-434-7736, or write to us at:
First Name*Last Name*Email*EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
©2020 Rockingham Insurance. All Rights Reserved.
Terms of Service
Privacy Policy
Agent Log In
